{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Custom Home Builders","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40105/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40105,"taskName":"Find a Custom Home Builder","taskDescription":"Build a Custom Home","xmTaskDescriptor":"Custom Home Builders","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1001,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"builder sites construction homes building","textMessagingName":"New Custom Home","rolloverLongDesc":"In true custom building, you choose everything including layout, lot size, and accessibility. Custom home building is often characterized as the most expensive new home construction option, however the price is dependent on your preferences and can be comparable to other types of new homes.","rolloverShortDesc":"Built from the ground up on land you own or are planning to purchase.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Build a Custom Home.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Custom Home Builders \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Construct a Custom Home","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":41,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Custom Home Builder","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Find a Custom Home Builder","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Custom Home Builder Need","urlName":"Find-a-Custom-Home-Builder","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Custom Home Builders - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"construction, builder, custom, house","emcCategoryOid":-12051,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your new home?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your new home","commentsPromptText":"Provide any additional details about your home building project:","primaryQuestionSetId":416,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40105/":{"taskOID":40105,"originalTaskOID":40105,"setID":416,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":502245,"questionDisplayText":"Modular home?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are you looking to build a modular home?","shortQuestionText":"Are you looking to build a modular home?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502246,"questionDisplayText":"# of Bedrooms","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many Bedrooms would you like in the custom home?","shortQuestionText":"How many Bedrooms would you like in the custom home?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9594,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4","answerDisplayText":"4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":505,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"5 or more","answerDisplayText":"5 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502247,"questionDisplayText":"# of Bathrooms","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many Bathrooms would you like in the custom home?","shortQuestionText":"How many Bathrooms would you like in the custom home?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9594,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4","answerDisplayText":"4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":505,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"5 or more","answerDisplayText":"5 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502248,"questionDisplayText":"Land Status","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the status of the land where the home will be built?","shortQuestionText":"What is the status of the land where the home will be built?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3122,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"I already own the land","answerDisplayText":"I already own the land","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17990,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"I am currently looking for land","answerDisplayText":"I am currently looking for land","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"I have not started looking for land","answerDisplayText":"I have not started looking for land","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17991,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"I am in process of purchasing land","answerDisplayText":"I am in process of purchasing land","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502249,"questionDisplayText":"Styles Interested in","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the styles of home you are interested in:","shortQuestionText":"Select the styles of home you are interested in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17980,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ranch","answerDisplayText":"Ranch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17976,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Log","answerDisplayText":"Log","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17978,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Mediterranean","answerDisplayText":"Mediterranean","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17979,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Modern","answerDisplayText":"Modern","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17972,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Bungalow","answerDisplayText":"Bungalow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17973,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Colonial","answerDisplayText":"Colonial","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17974,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Country","answerDisplayText":"Country","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17975,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Georgian","answerDisplayText":"Georgian","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17977,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Luxury","answerDisplayText":"Luxury","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17981,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Southwestern","answerDisplayText":"Southwestern","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17983,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Victorian","answerDisplayText":"Victorian","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502250,"questionDisplayText":"Approximate Budget","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What is the approximate budget for this custom home? (not including Land)","shortQuestionText":"What is the approximate budget for this custom home? (not including Land)","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17930,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Under $100,000","answerDisplayText":"Under $100,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17931,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$100,000 - $150,000","answerDisplayText":"$100,000 - $150,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17932,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$150,000 - $200,000","answerDisplayText":"$150,000 - $200,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17933,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"$200,000 - $250,000","answerDisplayText":"$200,000 - $250,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17934,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"$250,000 - $300,000","answerDisplayText":"$250,000 - $300,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17935,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"$300,000 - $400,000","answerDisplayText":"$300,000 - $400,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17936,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"$400,000 - $500,000","answerDisplayText":"$400,000 - $500,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203124,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Over $500,000","answerDisplayText":"Over $500,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502251,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Timing","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like the home to be completed? ","shortQuestionText":"When would you like the home to be completed? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17984,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17985,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3 - 6 months","answerDisplayText":"3 - 6 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17986,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6 - 9 months","answerDisplayText":"6 - 9 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17987,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"9 - 12 months","answerDisplayText":"9 - 12 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17988,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Over a year","answerDisplayText":"Over a year","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":502245,"questionDisplayText":"Modular home?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are you looking to build a modular home?","shortQuestionText":"Are you looking to build a modular home?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502246,"questionDisplayText":"# of Bedrooms","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many Bedrooms would you like in the custom home?","shortQuestionText":"How many Bedrooms would you like in the custom home?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9594,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4","answerDisplayText":"4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":505,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"5 or more","answerDisplayText":"5 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9594,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4","answerDisplayText":"4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":505,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"5 or more","answerDisplayText":"5 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502247,"questionDisplayText":"# of Bathrooms","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many Bathrooms would you like in the custom home?","shortQuestionText":"How many Bathrooms would you like in the custom home?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9594,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4","answerDisplayText":"4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":505,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"5 or more","answerDisplayText":"5 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9594,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4","answerDisplayText":"4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":505,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"5 or more","answerDisplayText":"5 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502248,"questionDisplayText":"Land Status","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the status of the land where the home will be built?","shortQuestionText":"What is the status of the land where the home will be built?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3122,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"I already own the land","answerDisplayText":"I already own the land","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17990,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"I am currently looking for land","answerDisplayText":"I am currently looking for land","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"I have not started looking for land","answerDisplayText":"I have not started looking for land","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17991,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"I am in process of purchasing land","answerDisplayText":"I am in process of purchasing land","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3122,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"I already own the land","answerDisplayText":"I already own the land","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17990,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"I am currently looking for land","answerDisplayText":"I am currently looking for land","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"I have not started looking for land","answerDisplayText":"I have not started looking for land","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17991,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"I am in process of purchasing land","answerDisplayText":"I am in process of purchasing land","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502249,"questionDisplayText":"Styles Interested in","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the styles of home you are interested in:","shortQuestionText":"Select the styles of home you are interested in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17980,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ranch","answerDisplayText":"Ranch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17976,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Log","answerDisplayText":"Log","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17978,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Mediterranean","answerDisplayText":"Mediterranean","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17979,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Modern","answerDisplayText":"Modern","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17972,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Bungalow","answerDisplayText":"Bungalow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17973,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Colonial","answerDisplayText":"Colonial","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17974,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Country","answerDisplayText":"Country","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17975,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Georgian","answerDisplayText":"Georgian","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17977,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Luxury","answerDisplayText":"Luxury","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17981,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Southwestern","answerDisplayText":"Southwestern","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17983,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Victorian","answerDisplayText":"Victorian","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":17980,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ranch","answerDisplayText":"Ranch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17976,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Log","answerDisplayText":"Log","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17978,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Mediterranean","answerDisplayText":"Mediterranean","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17979,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Modern","answerDisplayText":"Modern","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17972,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Bungalow","answerDisplayText":"Bungalow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17973,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Colonial","answerDisplayText":"Colonial","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17974,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Country","answerDisplayText":"Country","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17975,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Georgian","answerDisplayText":"Georgian","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17977,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Luxury","answerDisplayText":"Luxury","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17981,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Southwestern","answerDisplayText":"Southwestern","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17983,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Victorian","answerDisplayText":"Victorian","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502250,"questionDisplayText":"Approximate Budget","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What is the approximate budget for this custom home? (not including Land)","shortQuestionText":"What is the approximate budget for this custom home? (not including Land)","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17930,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Under $100,000","answerDisplayText":"Under $100,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17931,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$100,000 - $150,000","answerDisplayText":"$100,000 - $150,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17932,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$150,000 - $200,000","answerDisplayText":"$150,000 - $200,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17933,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"$200,000 - $250,000","answerDisplayText":"$200,000 - $250,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17934,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"$250,000 - $300,000","answerDisplayText":"$250,000 - $300,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17935,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"$300,000 - $400,000","answerDisplayText":"$300,000 - $400,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17936,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"$400,000 - $500,000","answerDisplayText":"$400,000 - $500,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203124,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Over $500,000","answerDisplayText":"Over $500,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":17930,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Under $100,000","answerDisplayText":"Under $100,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17931,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$100,000 - $150,000","answerDisplayText":"$100,000 - $150,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17932,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$150,000 - $200,000","answerDisplayText":"$150,000 - $200,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17933,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"$200,000 - $250,000","answerDisplayText":"$200,000 - $250,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17934,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"$250,000 - $300,000","answerDisplayText":"$250,000 - $300,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17935,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"$300,000 - $400,000","answerDisplayText":"$300,000 - $400,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17936,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"$400,000 - $500,000","answerDisplayText":"$400,000 - $500,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203124,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Over $500,000","answerDisplayText":"Over $500,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502251,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Timing","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like the home to be completed? ","shortQuestionText":"When would you like the home to be completed? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17984,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17985,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3 - 6 months","answerDisplayText":"3 - 6 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17986,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6 - 9 months","answerDisplayText":"6 - 9 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17987,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"9 - 12 months","answerDisplayText":"9 - 12 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17988,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Over a year","answerDisplayText":"Over a year","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":17984,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17985,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3 - 6 months","answerDisplayText":"3 - 6 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17986,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6 - 9 months","answerDisplayText":"6 - 9 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17987,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"9 - 12 months","answerDisplayText":"9 - 12 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17988,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Over a year","answerDisplayText":"Over a year","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}